traveltura.com 2019-06-07

# Traveltura Privacy Policy - TravelTura

GENERAL INFORMATION  
This Privacy Statement sets out how we comply with European Union data protection requirements.  
This applies to the entire web site. Any changes to these policies will be notified to you on the web  
site and will be included in the updated Privacy Statement. We reserve the right to modify this  
privacy policy at any time.  
You can also access this Privacy Statement via our homepage and from the bottom of every page by  
clicking on the appropriate link.  
Traveltura, its subsidiaries and affiliates are committed to respecting your privacy. We have  
structured our web site so that, in general, you can visit us on the web without identifying yourself  
or revealing any personal information. Once you choose to provide us with any information by  
which you can be identified, Then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with  
this Privacy Statement.  
For your protection, we are registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 and have given all  
appropriate notifications to the Information Commissioner.  

WHAT WE MAY COLLECT  
We may collect the following information as submitted to our web site by you: A contact name  
(you should ensure that you have the consent of any individual's details submitted), your phone  
and fax numbers, your Email address, your postal address, your preferred user name, additional  
information and your preferred password.  
We may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional  
interests, demographics, experiences with our products, and contact preferences in order to provide  
you with further correspondence about our products and services. Information about travel products  
or services may also be stored.  

WHAT DO WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER?  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service. We  
may use the information to improve our products and services and for research purposes.  
Our representatives will usually follow up, either by e-mail, phone, fax or mail, to people who have  
registered their details.  
We may periodically send promotional e-mail about new products, special offers or other  
information which we think you may find interesting using the e-mail address which you have  
provided.  
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.  
We may contact you by e-mail, phone, fax or mail.  
We will not disclose your private information to any third party companies or organisations other  
than those who would be the service provider for your purchase (I.e a hotel) or unless we are legally  
obliged to do so. Even if we must share your information with another party the details released will  
be kept to the strict minimum.  

WHO WE SHARE THE INFORMATION WITH AND YOUR CHOICES  
Some of your information will be shared with service providers (I.e hotels) to ensure that the  
service is carried out. Your details will not be given to and third party company not involved in the  
service purchased unless you give Traveltura your permission to do so.  

© Traveltura 2010. All Rights Reserved. 

Registered Address: Traveltura.com Ltd, 3 Littlestone Road, New Romney, Kent, TN28 8LN. Company No: 04276398 

Website designed and built by Digital Trip
